NATHANAEL GANDHI

MECHATRONIC ENGINEER



+61 431 905 747

nathanaelgandhi@gmail.com

New South Wales, Australia

NathanaelGandhi.com

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional engineer with five years of experience in electronic systems design and development. Strong teamwork, research and development skills. Projects & blog posts available on my website. The best way to get to know me is for us to have a chat.

SKILLS

- Embedded Software (C/C++)
- Electronic Design Automation
- · Prototyping, Soldering
- Strong Communication
- Managing Client Relations
- Autonomous Team Member
- CI & Containerized Development
- Linux Based Operating Systems

EXPERIENCE

AIT ENGINEER

Space Machines Company

2021 - Present

- Developed flight software in C derived from NASA software
- · Low-level hardware interactions & regression testing
- Designed and assembled electronics for engineering and flight
- Tested and reviewed spacecraft electrical components & systems

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Robotics Institute: University of Technology Sydney (F.K.A Centre for Autonomous Systems)

2018 - 2021

- Modeled and verified sensing technology using Matlab and ROS
- Built power conditioning and distribution PCBs & harnesses
- Mechanical lead for self-driving mobility platform

of Technology Sydney **EXECUTIVE**

Robotics Society: University of Technology Sydney 2018 - 2022

- 2020 2022 Treasurer | Events | Technical Advisor
- 2019 President
 - 24 events involving technical, industry and social aspects
 - Mentored 4 teams in interstate and local competitions
 - Hosted UTS information and experience tours

EDUCATION

BE(HONS) MECHATRONIC DipProfEngPrac

University of Technology Sydney 2017 - 2022

DIPLOMA OF ENGINEERING

UTS:Insearch

2016